# CURRICULUM VITAE GRACE OTUYA NYANGAYI

gracenyangayi@gmail.com | +254703286262 | P.O. Box 30271-00100

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

Gender: Female Nationality: Kenyan Marital Status: Single

Languages: English, Kiswahili

## **CAREER SUMMARY**

I am a BSc. Computer Science graduate with knowledge in Linux, Unix, and Microsoft systems. I have experience in computer networks, web conference systems and ICT systems support. I intend to grow my ICT skills as well as to learn various other attributes that will enhance my career growth and the growth of the organization in which I get the opportunity to work.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

#### Laravel Junior Developer | eMerge Student Management System Australia (From dec 2021-To date)

Key Responsibilities

- System Testing and Maintenance
- User Support
- Debugging
- System modifications

#### ICT Attaché | Kenya Forest Service (1st October 2020 – 31st December 2020)

Key Responsibilities

- Network Maintenance and Support (Router configuration)
- User Support
- System Testing and Maintenance
- Hardware Repair and Maintenance
- Computer Basic Skills

## Data Entry Clerk | Africa Management Solutions Limited (September 2020)

**Responsibilities** 

Capturing and managing the recruitment data for the organization.

# **EDUCATION**

**BACHELOR OF SCIENCE** | Computer Science – St Paul's University (2017–2020) Second Class Upper Division. **KENYA CERTIFICATE OF SECONDARY EDUCATION** – Booker Academy (2016) B plain **KENYA CERTIFICATE OF PRIMARY EDUCATION** – Kitale Academy Primary School (2012)

# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

#### **Professional Certificate**

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) – Cisco Networking Academy Introduction to Linux – Cisco Networking Academy Introduction to IoT – Cisco Networking academy Introduction to Cyber Security- Cisco Networking Academy Introduction to ICT support -Google

## **REFEREES**

Mr. Samuel Karuga H.O.D Computer

Science

St Paul's university

0721 435 257

skaruga@spu.ac.ke

Ms. Annabelle Obare Personal Banking Standard Chartered

Bank

annabelleobare@gmail.com

0723 615 013

Ms. Claudia Arunga Database

Administrator

Bushiangala technical

cmukula@bushiangalatechnical.ac.ke

0722904289